

CAO THI THANH HA

INTERN

I look forward to gaining more experience and knowledge, as well as working in a dynamic media and marketing environment. I always want to challenge myself in a professional environment to improve my experience in economics, law, marketing, and commerce

CAO THI THANH HA

thanhha09062002@gmail.com

0767348962

Ho Chi Minh City

EDUCATION

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY

ECONOMIC LAW

October 2020 - Present

SKILLS

OFFICE INFORMATICS

I have proficient skills in Office
Informatics: Word, PowerPoint, Excel

ENGLISH:

Basic English communication ability

THU DUC HIGH SCHOOL

SOCIAL SCIENCES DEPARTMENT

August 2017 - August 2020

Tốt nghiệp loại Khá, GPA: 8.0

WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2021 - 07/2021

TIEN PHONG COMMERCIAL JOINT STOCK BANK

SALES MAN

Advise customers on bank loan product packages. Support in making loan applications and customer care.

08/2021 - 11/2021

MINH TAM LAW FIRM

LAW INTERN

Drafting civil and administrative contracts.

Analyzing judgments and indictments. Research the provisions in the Law.

11/2021 - Present

ADMISSIONS & COMMUNICATIONS
OFFICE OF VAN LAN UNIVERSITY

ADMISSIONS CONSULTANT

Consulting on 61 professions and training faculties of Van Lang University for parents and candidates. Advice on how to prepare admission documents. Support in receiving admission applications based on transcripts, National High School Exam scores, and managing candidate data.

Organize documents, classify documents, check and compare dmission information. Go to high schools to advise 12th graders.

11/2023 - Present

VOICE OF VIETNAM (VOV) - VOV TRAFFIC CHANNEL (SOUTH REGION) **EDITORIAL INTERN**

Edit scripts and content according to each assigned category. - Search for interview characters, come up with ideas for questions to interact with the characters. Find information and reportage images about the assigned topic.

04/2024 - 06/2024

MITA MEDIA LIMITED

MARKETING INTERN

Edit scripts and content according to each assigned category. Search for customers, create information and plans for each category. Monitor and operate the program.

DƯ ÁN

03/2024 - 05/2024

HO CHI MINH CITY INTERNATIONAL GINSENG AND AROMA AND MEDICAL INGREDIENTS FESTIVAL

PLANNER - OPERATE

Follow the script & support the Media team throughout the event. Drafting contracts for partners.

Assist in writing press releases and media articles for all activities related to Sam Festival programs

Implement and coordinate program logistics, support response to requests from other teams/groups during the event

CERTIFICATE

2018

MOS Powerpoint Certificate

2024

MOS Word Certificate

Tháng 07/2024

APTIS ESOL - B1